let questions = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "Which of the following CSS property specifies the look and design of an outline?",
      answer: "a. outline-style",
      options: [
        "a. outline-style",
        "b. outline-format",
        "c. outline-font",
        "d. none of the mentioned"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "What will be the output of the following CSS code snippet?\nspan {\n	border: 1px solid red;\n    outline: green dotted thick;\n}",
      answer: "b. All span elements will have a red border and a green dotted outline",
      options: [
        "a. All span elements will have a green thick border and a red outline",
        "b. All span elements will have a red border and a green dotted outline",
        "c. All span elements will have an outer green dotted border and an inner red border",
        "d. All span elements will have an outer red border and inner green dotted border"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "Which of the following CSS property sets the shadow for a box element?",
      answer: "b. box-shadow",
      options: [
        "a. set-shadow",
        "b. box-shadow",
        "c. shadow",
        "d. canvas-shadow"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "Which of the following CSS property is used to set the color of the text?",
      answer: "d. color",
      options: [
        "a. text-decoration",
        "b. pallet",
        "c. colour",
        "d. color"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "Which of the following CSS Property controls how an element is positioned?",
      answer: "b. position",
      options: [
        "a. static",
        "b. position",
        "c. fix",
        "d. set"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "Which of the following CSS selector selects the elements that are checked?",
      answer: "a. :checked",
      options: [
        "a. :checked",
        "b. E ~ F",
        "c. ::after",
        "d. none of the mentioned"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "Which of the following CSS property is used to specify table borders in CSS?",
      answer: "d. none of the mentioned",
      options: [
        "a. table:border",
        "b. table",
        "c. border",
        "d. none of the mentioned"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "Which of the following property is used to align the text in a table?",
      answer: "d. none of the mentioned",
      options: [
        "a. text-align",
        "b. align",
        "c. text",
        "d. none of the mentioned"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "Which of the following CSS Property sets the stacking order of positioned elements?",
      answer: "b. z-index",
      options: [
        "a. y-index",
        "b. z-index",
        "c. x-index",
        "d. all of the mentioned"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "Which of the following property allows a marquee to be used in the case of a text-overflow?",
      answer: "b. overflow-style",
      options: [
        "a. overflow-marquee",
        "b. overflow-style",
        "c. overflow-text",
        "d. none of the mentioned"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "Which of the following is an appropriate value for the overflow element?",
      answer: "d. all of the mentioned",
      options: [
        "a. scroll",
        "b. hidden",
        "c. auto",
        "d. all of the mentioned"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "What will be the output of the following CSS code?\ndiv {\n    border-width:5px;	\n    border-style:dotted solid double dashed;\n}",
      answer: "a. Box having dotted bottom outline, solid right outline, double top outline and dashed left outline",
      options: [
        "a. Box having dotted bottom outline, solid right outline, double top outline and dashed left outline",
        "b. Box having dotted bottom outline, solid left outline, double top outline and dashed left outline",
        "c. Box having dotted top outline, solid right outline, double bottom outline and dashed left outline",
        "d. Box having dotted top outline, solid left outline, double bottom outline and dashed right outline"
      ]
    },
      {
        numb: 13,
        question: "How can you apply a style to an element with the id “header” in CSS?",
        answer: "A. #header",
        options: [
          "A. #header",
          "B. .header",
          "C. element:header",
          "D. header:"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 14,
        question: "Which property is used to change the background color of an element?",
        answer: "A. background-color",
        options: [
          "A. background-color",
          "B. color",
          "C. background",
          "D. bgcolor"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 15,
        question: "What does the “box-sizing” property in CSS control?",
        answer: "C. Box model sizing",
        options: [
          "A. Element visibility",
          "B. Box shadows",
          "C. Box model sizing",
          "D. Font size"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 16,
        question: "How do you center an element horizontally in CSS?",
        answer: "B. margin: auto;",
        options: [
          "A. text-align: center;",
          "B. margin: auto;",
          "C. align: center;",
          "D. horizontal-align: center;"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 17,
        question: "Which CSS pseudo-class is used to select and style an element when the mouse is over it?",
        answer: "A. :hover",
        options: [
          "A. :hover",
          "B. :active",
          "C. :focus",
          "D. :visited"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 18,
        question: "How do you set the font style to italic in CSS?",
        answer: "A. font-style: italic;",
        options: [
          "A. font-style: italic;",
          "B. font-weight: italic;",
          "C. style: italic;",
          "D. italic: true;"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 19,
        question: "Which CSS property is used for controlling the order of flexible items?",
        answer: "A. order",
        options: [
          "A. order",
          "B. flex-order",
          "C. arrange",
          "D. flex-item-order"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 20,
        question: "What is the purpose of the z-index property in CSS?",
        answer: "B. Controlling the stacking order of elements",
        options: [
          "A. Adjusting the font size",
          "B. Controlling the stacking order of elements",
          "C. Managing text alignment",
          "D. Defining the element width"
        ]
      }
    ];    